relevantradio.com 2018-06-14

# Donor Privacy Policy - Relevant Radio

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Statement.

###  **Collection of your Personal Information**

When making donations, Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. collects personal information, such as your email address, name, home or work address, and telephone number.  If you choose to make online donations, we will collect additional personal information, including your credit card number and billing address, in order to process the transaction.

###  **Use of your Personal Information**

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. collects and uses your personal information to deliver the services you have requested (such as email correspondence and credit card billing). Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. does not use or disclose any personal information without your explicit consent.

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. may contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. does not sell, rent, exchange or lease its customer lists to third parties.   We may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Immaculate Heart Media, Inc.; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. services or members of the public.

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. or its subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

###  **Control your Personal Information**

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. offers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may choose not to receive marketing material from Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. You may also stop the delivery of future promotional email from Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. by following the specific instructions in the email you receive. The instructions explain how to stop receiving such emails.

There are some Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. services that send out periodic emails informing you of technical service issues, service surveys, new feature announcements, and news about Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. products and services. You will not be able to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered a part of the service you have chosen.

###  **Security of your Personal Information**

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

###  **Use of Cookies**

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.  One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you register with the Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. site or services, a cookie helps Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to Immaculate Heart Media, Inc., the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. services or Web sites you visit.

### A note about the Relevant Radio App

The Relevant Radio app is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area.

###  **Enforcement of this Privacy Statement**

If you have questions regarding this statement, contact Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. at 1-877-291-0123.

###  **Changes to this Statement**

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. will use your personal information, Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. is protecting your information.

###  **Contact Information**

Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you believe that Immaculate Heart Media, Inc. has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us by telephone, email, or postal mail.

Email: info@relevantradio.com  
**  
** Immaculate Heart Media, Inc.  
PO Box 10707  
Green Bay, WI 54307-0707
